{
    "Questions":
    [
        {
        "Question":"When was Ethosh founded?",
        "Option1":"Dec 2011",
        "Option2":"Sept 2011",
        "Option3":"Jan 2012",
        "Option4":"June 2011",
        "Correct":"Sept 2011"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Where was Ethosh's second office?",
        "Option1":"Deccan Gymkhana",
        "Option2":"Pan mala",
        "Option3":"Kothrud",
        "Option4":"SB Road",
        "Correct":"Kothrud"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Who was the 1st employee of Ethosh?",
        "Option1":"Gaurang",
        "Option2":"Rahul",
        "Option3":"Jitendra",
        "Option4":"Azim",
        "Correct":"Gaurang"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Who framed the name Ethosh?",
        "Option1":"Rahul",
        "Option2":"Sucheta",
        "Option3":"Jitendra",
        "Option4":"Prakash",
        "Correct":"Jitendra"
        },
        {
        "Question":"What was Ethosh's highest employee strength in 2018?",
        "Option1":"45",
        "Option2":"42",
        "Option3":"46",
        "Option4":"41",
        "Correct":"46"
        },
        {
        "Question":"When did Ethosh move to the current office?",
        "Option1":"April 2017",
        "Option2":"March 2017",
        "Option3":"March 2018",
        "Option4":"April 2018",
        "Correct":"March 2017"
        },
        {
        "Question":"What service Ethosh doesn't offer?",
        "Option1":"VR",
        "Option2":"Animation",
        "Option3":"eDM",
        "Option4":"Tele-marketing",
        "Correct":"Tele-marketing"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Where did Ethosh not have office out of Pune?",
        "Option1":"Mumbai",
        "Option2":"Delhi",
        "Option3":"Pittsburg",
        "Option4":"San Diego",
        "Correct":"Delhi"
        },
        {
        "Question":"Where is Ethosh's current US office?",
        "Option1":"New York",
        "Option2":"Pittsburg",
        "Option3":"San Jose",
        "Option4":"Los Angeles",
        "Correct":"Pittsburg"
        },
        {
        "Question":"How many cabins Ethosh's current office has?",
        "Option1":"4",
        "Option2":"2",
        "Option3":"5",
        "Option4":"6",
        "Correct":"5"
        }
    ]
}
